       0.0 ms   the process starts
       0.0 ms   tui_live + the variant are imported (already done by now)
     137.4 ms   Data() - the lyric timeline, 98 lines
loading the film's shot table...
    3461.9 ms   Engine() - the film's 97-shot table
       9.9 ms   Screen()
    2812.5 ms   school_fx.warm() - 244 sprites + the basketball animation
      67.4 ms   the first draw() + rasterise

total: from the import of the modules to the first finished frame, the user sees a blank screen for everything above 'the first draw()'
